MITALI CHAVAN

Phone · 9359254340
Email · onlymituinsymbi@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile · Mitali Chavan. |
LinkedIn

Human Resource graduate. People Oriented person with strong Communication and Interpersonal skills. To seek employment as a HR Executive at one of the leading companies to devote my skills to a company that will appreciate and recognize my expertise. Well-acquainted with HR databases, hiring procedure, Recruitment activities, Interviewing candidates, Employee Engagement.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INTELLECT DESIGN ARENA LTD.

JULY 2021 TO JAN 2023

TALENT ACQUISITION EXECUTIVE

- Responsible for full life-cycle recruiting and hiring for IT positions (Delivery/ Solutions/ Management)
- Collaborated with hiring managers to understand technical job duties, responsibilities, staffing needs and business requirements.
- Coordinated all interviews for candidates
- Negotiated all job offers, wrote and delivered all offer letters, Onboarding process.

KSB TECH PVT. LTD. JAN 2020 TO MAR 2021

MANAGEMENT TRAINEE- HR & OD

Recruitment (IT Recruitment)

- Working as a Full cycle recruiter, sourcing, screening, interviewing, selection.
- Work closely with hiring managers in various departments to define recruitment needs and plan the hiring process
- Source candidates on job boards, resume databases, professional networks and through referrals, releasing IJP's.
- Interview candidates through various platform (phone screening calls, Skype video interviews and in-person meetings) initiated online test for the shortlisted candidates through online platform "CoCubes".
- Conducted reference and background checks, processed medical benefits enrollment and new hire packet. Responsible for updating and entering new employees into database system
- · Preparing Offer letters for selected candidates.

Employee Engagement

• Virtual Funtastic Day- Every month independently conducted Virtual Funtastic Day with various departments, connected our employees virtually to replenish the fun.

į

ì

Health Knowledge Sharing- Co-ordinated every 2 months various Health Session i.e.,
 Correctposture for work from home. How to Manage Diabetics and Thyroid effectively.
 Stress Management and Mental Awareness.

Workday (HRIS System) Implementation

- Initially worked on functional & Integration test cases on workday tenant.
- Checking the results on SFTP file whether changes in test cases reflecting or not.
- Data Gathering completed within time span in HCM Workbook.
- · Daily communicating with Germany counter for updates.

Other HR Operations

- Responsible for designing, implementation of company policies.
- Preparation of HR monthly report.
- Responsible for preparation of Salary offer to selected employees.
- Preparing various Training announcement and circulate to the employees.
- Responsible for preparing creative presentations for new proposals for organizational development.
- · Collaborated and worked with HR Team on HRIS system "HR Mantra" and "Workday".
- · Maintaining data base in excel and HRIS system.
- · Worked on online training platform "Percipio".
- Closely coordinated with vendors for various functions, such as Recruitment consultant, Conducting Knowledge Sharing Sessions, R&R Gift vouchers distribution.
- Responsible for complete process of handling gift and certificates under Reward and Recognition.
- Daily thought of the day circulation to motivate employees with positive note.

CPHR SERVICES PVT. LTD.

JAN 2019 TO NOV 2019

SR. RECRUITMENT EXECUTIVE (IT Recruitment)

- Managing the complete Recruitment life cycle for sourcing the best talent through diverse sources after identification of requirement.
- Built talented pool of quality, skilled candidates, placed individuals in successful positions and gained reputation for sourcing top-quality applicants.
- Candidate Pre-Screening: short listing candidates sourced through portal (Naukri, LinkedIn) social media platform and validating them on their experience and interest.
- Analyzed various job applications and filtered candidates through telephonic or one on one interviews.
- Assisted for In-house Recruitment across organization.
- Conducting new employee orientations and serving as a consultant to management for the on boarding process to leaving formalities and Documentation.
- Established and maintained good relationships between employers and employees.
- Manage the organization's employee database and prepare reports.
- Conducting events i.e., Birthdays, Annual Day, Every Friday Lunch Day, Picnics, etc.

RUBICON (Skill Development and Training) **JAN 2018 TO MAR 2018**

STAFFING SPECIALIST (IT RECRUITMENT)

- Manage the In-house Recruitment and client requirements, shortlisting and sourcing profiles for various streams.
- Scheduling and coordinating interviews via phone calls, in person, VC.
- · Conducted weekend drives for technology teams.
- · Keeping strong follow up with candidates.

EXL SERVICES PVT. LTD.

OCT 2013 TO JAN 2014

ASSOCIATE- (BACK-OFFICE INSURANCE PORCESS)

EDUCATION

PES MODERN COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING (PUNE UNIVERSITY)

2016

MASTER'S IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (HUMAN RESOURCE)

SYMBIOSIS COLLEGE OF ARTS & COMMERCE (PUNE UNIVERSITY)

2013

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

SYMBIOSIS COLLEGE OF ARTS & COMMERCE (PUNE UNIVERSITY)

2009

HSC-COMMERCE

SKILLS

- HR Operations
- Employee Engagement
- Effective Communication Skills
- Knowledge of MS
 Office (Excel/Word/
 PowerPoint)

- Recruitment
- HR Information System (Workday/ HRMantra)

ACADEMIC PROJECT UNDERTAKEN SPES MANAGEMENT LTD – 2015

RECRUITMENT END TO END PROCESS

- Ensuring the recruitment and selection process is followed.
- Advertising on job portals, conducting interviews, and coordinating with Functional Heads & ProjectManagers for ensuring successful hiring.
- Salary negotiation with shortlisted employees and making them aware of the salary structure &policies the organization is following. Verification Process.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: 1st March 1991

Hobbies: Drawing, Sketching, Internet surfing, Swimming, Travelling

DECLARATION:

I hereby declare that all the information mentioned in my resume is true and correct to my knowledge and I take full responsibility for the accuracy of the particulars mentioned.

PLACE: PUNE SIGNATURE

DATE: (MITALI CHAVAN)